<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pureWriter">Pure Writer</string>
    <string name="about">About | ガイド</string>
    <string name="hintDrawerHeader">速く、優れた経験、決して失われたコンテンツ</string>
    <string name="editorTipAMenu">あなたは、テキストを選択する必要があります</string>
    <string name="redo">遣り直す</string>
    <string name="undo">アンドゥ</string>
    <string name="editorHintContent">テキストを入力してください</string>
    <string name="titleHint">タイトルを入力してください</string>
    <string name="share">シェア</string>
    <string name="copyTitle">コピータイトル</string>
    <string name="lock">保護</string>
    <string name="history"><b>歴史</b></string>
    <string name="tipShouldUnlock">最初にロックを解除する必要があります</string>
    <string name="tipShouldSetupFingerprint">指紋を最初に作成する必要があります</string>
    <string name="sendContentTo">このコンテンツを送信する：</string>
    <string name="failedTitleIsEmpty">失敗：タイトルが空です</string>
    <string name="failedContentIsEmpty">失敗：コンテンツが空です</string>
    <string name="copyTheTitleSuccessfully">タイトルを正常にコピーしました</string>
    <string name="copyTheContentSuccessfully">コンテンツを正常にコピーしました</string>
    <string name="tipDestroyArticleSuccessfully">この記事を正常に破棄し、履歴ページから元に戻すことができます</string>
    <string name="titleAndContentAreEmpty">タイトルと内容が空であります</string>
    <string name="clearThisPage">Clear this page</string>
    <string name="copyContent">コンテンツをコピーする</string>
    <string name="appRecommendationTitle">推奨</string>
    <string name="appPureMosaic">PureMosaic</string>
    <string name="wordCountShort">単語数</string>
    <string name="historyState">保存されました</string>
    <string name="todayIs">今日</string>
    <string name="tipNeedFingerprint">表示と編集のために指紋を解除する必要があります</string>
    <string name="empty">空の</string>
    <string name="untitled">無題</string>
    <string name="isRevertToThisFile">このファイルに戻す？</string>
    <string name="noMore">もういや</string>
    <string name="tipNoMoreAndLimitFormat">もうこれ以上 %d ヒストリーしか保存できません</string>
    <string name="goOn">続ける</string>
    <string name="reject">拒絶する</string>
    <string name="titleIntroCard">何かを書くのに使う</string>
    <string name="defaultContent">あなたに会えてよかった！\nこれは簡単なプレーンテキストエディタです。元に戻ることができれば幸いです: <b>純粋な、安全な、いつでも、信頼性の高いコンテンツを失うことはありません。</b>\nこれは、Androidのプラットフォーム上で完璧な行間隔を確保し、ここでスペーシングを実現し、テキストをより快適で明瞭に見せると同時にスムーズなスクロール、ソフトキーボードを閉じるためのスワイプ、 ザ。\nシンプリシティは隠された複雑さです。あなたは成功を中断することができ、無料で、指紋でテキストを素早く暗号化することができます。\n最も重要な、<b>誤ってテキストを削除したり、すぐに電源を切ったりしても、履歴から回復することはできます。</b>\n記事の書き込みが完了したら、[送信]ボタンを使用して他のAppsに送信するか、新しい記事を開くことができます。\n今、あなたはこのページをクリアしてあなたの創造を試みることができます。創造の名は最も重要な財宝です。\nそれをお楽しみください。</string>
    <string name="defaultTitle">あなたの好きなように</string>
    <string name="tipPermissionFailed">権限の取得に失敗し、レコードを保存できません</string>
    <string name="titleStorePermissionFailed">記憶域アクセス要求に失敗しました</string>
    <string name="tipMessageStoragePermissionToSettings">履歴を保存するにはストレージ権限が必要です。設定ページにアクセスして権限を手動で付与する必要があります。そうしないと、履歴機能を正常に使用できません。</string>
    <string name="actionOkGoSettings">OK</string>
    <string name="tipFingerAuthRetry">失敗したロックを解除する指紋認証、再試行の残りの数：%d</string>
    <string name="tipFingerAuthFailed">指紋のロックを解除できませんでした.1分後にもう一度お試しください。プログラムが終了しようとしています…</string>
    <string name="tipTitleLengthLimit">タイトルは最大 100 文字をサポートします</string>
    <string name="tipRichText">Pure Writerは、純粋で良好なプレーンテキストライティングエクスペリエンスを作成することを約束しているため、リッチテキストコンテンツをサポートすることは意図されていません。 現時点では、太字をTXTファイルで表現できないため、<b>太字</b>のテキストが表示されます。太字は非表示、非表示です。ごめんなさい、ご容赦ください！ より良い提案がある場合は、フィードバックグループに参加して、私に教えてください、あなたのサポートに感謝します！</string>
    <string name="settings">設定</string>
    <string name="tipIndent">注：セグメンテーションのインデント設定項目では、既存のテキストは変更されません</string>
    <string name="format">フォーマット</string>
    <string name="indent">インデント</string>
    <string name="explanation">説明</string>
    <string name="tipInsertBlankLines">If this setting is Yes, when copying or sending text, it will automatically insert a blank line after each line of the text, because there is no good spacing in other Applications.</string>
    <string name="deleteObsoleteFiles">廃止されたファイルを削除する</string>
    <string name="dayNightMode">ナイトモード</string>
    <string name="summaryPay">Unlock advanced features</string>
    <string name="tipSettingNotSupport">一時的にこれを設定することはできません。 近日公開。</string>
    <string name="settingsAndRecommendation">設定とマイアプリ</string>
    <string name="on">オープン</string>
    <string name="off">クローズ</string>
    <string name="shortcutBar">ショートカットバー</string>
    <string name="insertBlankLinesWhenExporting">Insert blank lines when exporting</string>
    <string name="contentTextSize">コンテンツのテキストサイズ</string>
    <string name="iKnow">I know</string>
    <string-array name="nightModeEntries">
        <item>オート</item>
        <item>はい</item>
        <item>いいえ</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="tipMessageStoragePermissionFirst">あなたの記事を自動的にバックアップする許可が必要です。あなたの記事が失われないように、許可を与えてください。</string>
    <string name="promptShortcutTitle">簡単な説明 (optional)</string>
    <string name="promptShortcutContent">Content (require)</string>
    <string name="createShortcut">Create text Shortcut</string>
    <string name="noteShortcutCursorIndex">Please move the cursor position in the content to set the placement of the cursor after inserting the article</string>
    <string name="indentShort">Indent</string>
    <string name="delete">削除</string>
    <string name="messageDeleteShortcut">Click OK to delete this shortcut</string>
    <string name="features">特徴</string>
    <string name="sendTextFailedForTooLarge">あなたのテキストが長すぎるともう一つのアプリに直接送られる。それは、すでにあなたのクリップボードにテキストをコピー</string>
    <string name="hasSavedToYourAlbum">Saved to your album</string>
    <string name="previewAndSaveAs">Preview | Save as…</string>
    <string name="preview">プレビュー</string>
    <string name="tipRequirePro">Need to buy Pure Writer Pro</string>
    <string name="proReadMe">PureWriterが素晴らしいと思って、それがより良くなることを願ったら、開発者のインセンティブとして少しのお金を費やしたいですか？\n\nこれにより、私たちは良い方向に固執し、良心の製品を作り、より多くの独立した開発者を鼓舞することができます。\n\n「GOOGLE PLAY」ボタンをクリックすると、Google Pay Paymentを開くことができます。返品として、Pure Writerは広告なしの状態とすべてのProコンテンツを提供します。ありがとうございました！</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cancel">キャンセル</string>
    <string name="yes">OK</string>
    <string name="no">キャンセル</string>
    <string name="summaryPaid">Acquired: Pure Writer Pro</string>
    <string name="update">更新</string>
    <string name="labelUpdate">A new Pure Writer %1$s is available</string>
    <string name="messageDeleteArticlesToTrash">これらの記事を削除してゴミ箱に移動しますか？</string>
    <string name="tipPurchasedStatusFailed">Purchased. If the status is not refreshed, try clicking the Pro item again and will NOT deduct your money again.</string>
    <string name="createNew">新しい記事</string>
    <string name="autoLock">オートロック</string>
    <string name="enabled">有効</string>
    <string name="appLinks">Android リンク</string>
    <string name="titleOpenImportedFile">外部ファイルを開いたことが判明しました。アクションを選択してください</string>
    <string name="copied">コピーされた</string>
    <string name="sort">ソートタイプ</string>
    <string name="sortTypeDescModification">変更時刻の降順でソート</string>
    <string name="sortTypeDescCreation">作成時間の降順でソート</string>
    <string name="warningSavedFailed">ファイルを保存できませんでした。フルテキストをコピーしてから、アプリケーションを再起動してコンテンツが欠落していないか確認してください</string>
    <string name="backupNow">今すぐバックアップする</string>
    <string name="summaryBackup">バックアップファイルはパス/sdcard/backups/PureWriterBackup.dbに保存されます。</string>
    <string name="restoreTheBackup">バックアップを復元する</string>
    <string name="summaryRestoreTheBackup">The backup file will be read from the path /sdcard/backups/PureWriterBackup.db and your WebDAV cloud disk</string>
    <string name="backupSuccessfully">バックアップが成功しました</string>
    <string name="restoreSuccessfully">バックアップを正常に復元する</string>
    <string name="tipRestoreTheBackup">"Pure Writer's history files are only in the /sdcard/PureWriter directory. If you're about to use your backup files to restore content. The original PureWriter directory will be renamed to PureWriter.old, and then we will create a new PureWriter directory with the backup files. \n\nThe following is all the backup files, click to restore the backup: "</string>
    <string name="tipBackupNotExist">バックアップファイルは存在しません。 バックアップファイルを/sdcard/backups/PureWriterBackup.dbに入れてもう一度お試しください</string>
    <string name="wordCountMode">単語数</string>
    <string-array name="wordCountModeEntries">
        <item>スペースと改行を除外する</item>
        <item>すべてのシンボルとテキストを含める</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="fab">ホームフローティングボタン</string>
    <string name="tipFab">Tip: Long press it on the home page can hide it temporarily</string>
    <string name="tipCannotCreateNewWhenEmpty">New article can not be created when both title and content are empty</string>
    <string name="more">もっと</string>
    <string name="notSupportOpeningTheLink">Not support opening the link</string>
    <string name="formatters">Formatters</string>
    <string name="formatterSpace">Insert a space between Chinese and English</string>
    <string name="formatterIndent">Insert indentation at the beginning of all paragraphs</string>
    <string name="formatterLineBreak">Leave a blank line between the paragraphs</string>
    <string name="formatterRemoveBreak">Remove all blank lines between the paragraphs</string>
    <string name="titleAsAWordForACount">As a word for a count</string>
    <string name="trash">くずかご</string>
    <string name="papers">紙</string>
    <string name="defaultDark">デフォルトダーク</string>
    <string name="pureWhite">真っ白</string>
    <string name="custom">カスタム</string>
    <string name="apply">適用</string>
    <string name="promptCustomPaper">色または画像のURL</string>
    <string name="readMeCustomPaper">Please enter the RGB color value or image URL, such as #000000 or https://unsplash.com/photos/x.jpg</string>
    <string name="titleAlignCenter">Title center alignment</string>
    <string name="tipShortcutBarEnabled">閉じるのはお勧めしません</string>
    <string name="open">オープン</string>
    <string name="summaryAutoBackup">Automatically back up when files changed and exit, retaining up to 25 recent backup files</string>
    <string name="migratingData">データの移行</string>
    <string name="autoBackup">自動バックアップ</string>
    <string name="summaryDeleteObsoleteFiles">現在、プライベートディレクトリを使用してすべてのコンテンツを保存しています。 これをクリックすると、SDカードに残っている履歴ファイルの古いバージョンが削除されます</string>
    <string name="tipArticleDeleting">記事が削除されている、一時的に操作できない</string>
    <string name="noHistory">歴史はありません</string>
    <string name="formatterRemoveIndent">インデントを削除</string>
    <string name="keepScreenOn">画面をオンにする</string>
    <string name="gfmBreaksEnabled">改行で折り返す</string>
    <string name="gfmBreaksDisabled">実際に改行を表示するには2つの改行が必要です</string>
    <string name="wordCountTotal">すべての記事数</string>
    <string name="wordCountTotalValue">すべての記事の語数</string>
    <string name="timeMachineGuide">これは何ですか？ チャットウィンドウとして、または一時的にコンテンツを記録する場所、またはGoogle Assistantのようなものとして理解できます。 実際、「Time Machine」という名前があります。 はじめまして！</string>
    <string name="copyDate">日付のコピー</string>
    <string name="folders">フォルダ</string>
    <string name="defaultFolder">デフォルトフォルダ</string>
    <string name="summaryOfAbout">このアプリケーション用に開発して設計したオリジナルのアイデアやコンセプトについて学びます。</string>
    <string name="createNewFolder">新しいフォルダを作成する</string>
    <string name="emptyTip">記事はまだ開かれていません</string>
    <string name="name">名</string>
    <string name="optionalDescription">説明（オプション）</string>
    <string name="createFolder">フォルダーを作る</string>
    <string name="openSourceLicenses">オープンソースライセンス</string>
    <string name="cannotDelete">削除できません</string>
    <string name="cannotDeleteNotEmptyFolder">あなたが削除したい場合は、このフォルダに含まれている記事を削除してください、もう一度やり直してください</string>
    <string name="moveTo">へ引っ越す</string>
    <string name="move">移動</string>
    <string name="timeMachine">タイムマシン</string>
    <string name="listFirst">起動時にリストを開く</string>
    <string name="language">言語</string>
    <string name="followSystem">システムに従う</string>
    <string name="toastCannotRetrieveSelectedImage">選択した画像を取得できません</string>
    <string name="localPicture">ローカル写真</string>
    <string name="selectPicture">画像を選択</string>
    <string name="picture">画像</string>
    <string name="saved">保存された</string>
    <string name="sendTo">Send To</string>
    <string name="mode">モード</string>
    <string name="plainText">テキスト</string>
    <string name="tipHasNotPermissionWithAutoBackup">Attempt to auto backup failed because you did not give Pure Writer storage permission</string>
    <string name="hideTitleBarWhenPreviewingMarkdown">Hide title bar when previewing Markdown</string>
    <string name="summaryJoinBeta">Click to join the Beta update channel, you can get the latest update as soon as possible, but Beta update frequency will be very high, if you can not accept, please do not join.</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicy">個人情報保護方針</string>
    <string name="joinBeta">Join Beta</string>
    <string name="beforeRestoringYourBackup">beforeRestoringYourBackup</string>
    <string name="trashDescription">削除した記事を取得する</string>
    <string name="messageDeleteArticlesDirectly">これらの記事を直接削除する</string>
    <string name="trashFolderTip">あなたはゴミ箱フォルダにあり、このフォルダは新しい記事を作成できません。</string>
    <string name="tipLandscapeOrientation">横置きモードで外付けキーボードを使用してください</string>
    <string name="promptShortcutOrder">Order</string>
    <string name="editShortcut">Edit text Shortcut</string>
    <string name="fixedSync">同期</string>
    <string name="upload">アップロード</string>
    <string name="download">ダウンロード</string>
    <string name="titleBackupsAndSync">Backup and cloud sync</string>
    <string name="summaryBackupsAndSync">バックアップ、復元、WebDAV</string>
    <string name="syncNetwork">Cloud Backup Network</string>
    <string name="syncOnlyWifi">Automatic backup to WebDAV cloud disk is only allowed on Wi-Fi network</string>
    <string name="syncAllNetworks">Automatic backup to WebDAV cloud disk on all networks</string>
    <string name="webDavRootURL">WebDAV URL</string>
    <string name="webDavAccount">WebDAV Account</string>
    <string name="webDavPassword">WebDAV Password</string>
    <string name="webDavAutoBackup">Auto backup to WebDAV cloud disk</string>
    <string name="errorWebDavConfig">Your WebDAV configuration is incomplete or incorrect. Please modify the WebDAV configuration before attempting to upload</string>
    <string name="uploadSuccessful">アップロードに成功しました</string>
    <string name="fetchSuccessful">ダウンロードが成功しました</string>
    <string name="messageUpload">Pure Writer created a fixed file on your cloud disk. The file name is <b>PureWriter.txt</b>. You can click "OK" to upload the content of your current article to this fixed file. Then you can edit this cloud file on other devices. When it changes, you can pull it down. \n\nDo you now want to write the current article content to that cloud file?</string>
    <string name="typewriterMode">Typewriter Mode</string>
    <string name="edit">編集</string>
    <string name="editFolder">フォルダを編集する</string>
    <string name="shareText">推荐：纯纯写作，一个令人感到安心、拥有历史记录、多重防止文章丢失功能，和许多写作辅助的编辑器：https://writer.drakeet.com</string>
    <string name="shareMessage">如果你喜欢和支持纯纯写作，请帮忙点击右侧的分享按钮与你的朋友推荐这个应用，这对于它来说意义重大，纯纯写作将因为你的支持而能够变得更好，并不断开发、完善下去，非常感谢！\n\n了解更多关于纯纯写作：https://writer.drakeet.com</string>
    <string name="wordCountLong">単語数</string>
    <string name="wordCountOfCurrentArticle">現在の記事の単語数</string>
    <string name="floatingWordCount">Floating Word Count</string>
    <string name="tipFloatingWordCountDisabled">After you disable Word Count, you will be able to see it in TimeMachine.</string>
    <string name="reduceDatabaseSize">データベースサイズを縮小する</string>
    <string name="deleteSuccessfully">Deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="reduceDatabaseSizeMessage">すべての記事のすべての履歴を削除します。\n歴史だけでは、記事自体は削除されません。\n\n削除する前にバックアップを作成することをお勧めします。\n\nEnglish: \nDelete all history of all articles. \nJust history, the article itself will not be deleted. \n\nYou\'d better make a backup before you delete it.</string>
    <string name="unlockPro">Get Pro</string>
    <string name="presetTitle1">Pure Writer - Never Lost Content Editor</string>
    <string name="presetContent1">Pure Writer is an app that is dedicated to providing a fastest, excellent writing experience without losing content. When you look at the feedback in the Google Play Store for Pure Writer from users all over the world, you can find a large number of users exaggerating praise for Pure Writer, such as "have never used such a good app", "the most satisfied App", "Love this app", "Great"… As the only developer of this application, it is really gratifying…\nOne day in the end of June 2017, after experiencing various text-missing events caused by other editor applications and experiencing a variety of unsatisfactory and rough writing products, I was determined to develop such a application to obtain peace of mind, provide writing assistance, and actually designing and developing from the perspective of an author.\nPrior to this, I was responsible for independently developing a new editor for the "Zi" application during my spare time. At that time we spent a lot of effort on the rich text editor. Although we finally failed to implement a high-performance rich text editor that we were satisfied with on Android, in the process I invented many unique and useful technologies. Those technologies are more than enough to develop a pure text editor.\nSo Pure Writer was born. It started with a perfect line spacing and segment spacing function on Android and achieved full system compatibility and native performance. This is a unique technique for Pure Writer. In addition to Microsoft’s Office Word, it is difficult for you to find an editor that supports segment spacing and stable line spacing on mobile phones. And Office Word’s installation package is a few times to Pure Writer.\nIn addition to the unique segment spacing, Pure Writer also provides "Starting to enter the editing page immediately" and a unique "history record" function. Especially the historical record function, actually as a writer, I know that the historical record function is really important. It allows you to have a rare sense of peace of mind when writing, and Pure Writer will ensure that your content will never be lost. Even if you mistakenly delete the text, or instantly power off, you will still be able to recover it from history. The advantage of this is that everyone can pause and resume writing at any time, and with the soft keyboard status recording and recovery, switching back and forth will make people feel particularly smooth and comfortable.\nIn addition, Pure Writer also supports "quick shortcut bar" and "formatting tools". The quick shortcut bar allows users to define shortcut words and phrases; the formatting panel can help users quickly adjust the format of the articles, for example, between Chinese and English. Automatically insert spaces, or automatically indent adjustments and more.\nIn addition to achieving these remarkable features, Pure Writer has also worked hard on the details of the experience, it has a perfect keyboard response logic. When using Pure Writer, you can quickly slide down the page or shortcut bar to collapse the soft keyboard; after clicking on a certain line of the article, you can dynamically obtain the appropriate cursor focus position; when you close the soft keyboard, the article will keep your position… Many of these details, when you compare the use of other editor Apps, you will find Pure Writer is better and nice.\nAs for the base functions of an editor, Pure Writer has not fallen, such as automatic paragraph indentation, long picture generation, floating word count, undo/redo, Markdown, paper, fingerprint lock, night mode, word association, fast scroller, save as files, and so on. But even then, Pure Writer still maintains a simple and concise design style. It follows Material Design, and I also painted an icon like a Doraemon’s Time Machine, meaning that words can connect to the past, and thinking about the future. It is also responds to the "history record" function provided by Pure Writer.\nToday, the development of Pure Writer has submitted 1000 code commits, and the code has changed more than 100,000 lines. It took almost all my spare time, but I am very happy that more and more people have told me that they are particularly fond of this application. I am very enthusiastic about communicating with users, collecting feedback, and constantly improving. This made me feel more happy than ever and wanted to come and do something that was meaningful and worth investing for a long time.\nThanks to all the friends that have supported and helped me in this process. Without you, this application can’t be done better step by step, and it won’t be able to maintain the update for a long time. That’s great… And so today I can finally write such an article introduces the original intentions of Pure Writer, and its many "great features", hoping to make more people aware of this product, and we hope that we can record more moving and leave more memories in the years of our lives. May the words take us through time, connect with the past, and think about the future.</string>
    <string name="presetTitle2">Never Lost Content</string>
    <string name="presetContent2">So far, So far, Pure Writer has many lines of defense to avoid article loss: \n1. Once the article changes, it will trigger automatic saving. If it fails, it will immediately tell and warn the user.\n2. Check the article every 2 seconds whether the article is saved, and whether it is equivalent to the contents which was in the database, if it fails, immediately tell and warn the user. \n3. If the save fails, you can not actually exit the application. Pressing the exit button is equivalent to pressing the Home button. This give the user the opportunity to save by yourself as much as possible.\n4. Each time you turn to the background or quit the application, if the article changes, it will automatically back up the entire database. The backup content can be restored at any time. \n5. Provide history, undo and redo for Articles. \n6. Provide trash folder to avoid accidentally deleting articles\n7. Cloud backup. If you configure a WebDAV, Pure Writer will enable cloud backup by default, and automatically put your db database file (include all articles) sync to the cloud.</string>
    <string name="presetTitle3">Pure Writer Pro</string>
    <string name="presetContent3">If you think Pure Writer is great, and hope that it can be better, are you willing to spend a little money as an incentive for the developer?\nThis enables us to stick to good direction, create conscience products, and inspire more independent developers.\nYou can enter \"Settings > Pure Writer Pro\" to open Google Pay Payment. As a return, Pure Writer will provide ad-free state and all Pro contents for you including Custom Paper and Save As. Thank you very much!\nIf you have any question or request, feel free to contact me: \ndrakeet.me@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="presetTitle4">Pure Writer - Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="presetContent4">Pure Writer pays great attention to the privacy of users, and it will never collect any of your private content. \nIn addition, Pure Writer will never modify or read your clipboard content without permission or notice. \nPure Writer has applied for storage permissions only for file export and automatic backup. In addition, it will not read or modify any files in your external storage without permission or notice, and you can completely refuse to grant storage permissions, but doing so will result in loss of automatic backup functionality. \nIn particular, Pure Writer will never upload any of your articles, but because the title of the article as a file name may generate errors, Pure Writer will obtain your article title when the article title causes a crash error.</string>
    <string name="createAt">作成日</string>
    <string name="updatedAt">更新日</string>
    <string name="forcedBlackTextColor">強制黒色フォント</string>
    <string name="forcedWhiteTextColor">強制白色フォント</string>
    <string name="paragraphSpacing">段落の間隔</string>
    <string name="summaryExporting">段落の間隔が有効な場合にのみ有効です</string>
</resources>
